Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H .Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,July 25, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertie Palmer,July 25, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertie Palmer,July 27, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,July 31, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Pruda,July 31, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 11, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 22, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 31, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),August 3, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),August 14, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),August 22, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),August 30, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron W. Finley,August 1, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Carleton,August 3, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jennie Slack Cook,August 6, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 7, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harold, Geraldine, and Charles,August 9, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Hazel Helmer,August 11, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alta and the Girls,August 11, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Martha Olsen and Charles Crittenden,August 12, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Maud and Nettie Green,August 13, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Waterman,August 13, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and Father From: Eugene Chapel,August 14, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: R. W. Tenny,August 15, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary Marks,August 15, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice,August 23, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,August 25, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,August 28, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. H. Davis,September 30, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. H. Davis,undated (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),September 7, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),September 13, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),September 27, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: A. L. Foster,September 1, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertie and Henry Palmer,September 3, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Fred, Rose,September 6, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Correspondence to: W.H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 7, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ethel Stone,September 11, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. H. Davis,September 14, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Geraldine Gumbert,September 19, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Grandpa, Mother (NDF), and Harry Finley,September 19, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,September 24, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff and All,September 24, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Fanny Harris,September 26, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dora Wheeler,September 27, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Correspondence to: W.H. Davis, From: Harry Davis,September 28, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),October 5, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),October 9, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),October 18, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertie Palmer,October 5, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: R. W. Terry,October 11, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,October 13, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 144)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sadie and Bertie McMurtrie,October 15, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: William Lewis,October 22, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,October 30, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,October 26, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 148)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 1, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 149)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna Honeywell,November 27, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Correspondence to: W.H. Davis From: Harry DavisNovember 28, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Correspondence to: W.H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe DavisDecember 27, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Correspondence to: W.H. Davis and Family From: Jud and MatieDecember 1933 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty DavisDecember 3, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna HowardDecember 17, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Thomas, Edyth, Marvin,December 18, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jennie Slack Cook,December 19, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 157)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,December 19, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Carleton,December 21, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),December 26, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary Marks,December 28, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 161)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,[no month, day], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Clark Olmsted,January 1, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 163)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ma Honeywell,January 2, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,January 9, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie,January 25, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harold,January 30, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,February 5, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 26, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March [no day], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,March [no day], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,March 3, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 172)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,March 16, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie,March 18, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 174)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 24, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 10, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 176)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 21, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,April 3, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,April 24, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 179)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jessie,April 6, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 180)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna Honeywell,May 6, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,May 18, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Harry C. Finley,May 23, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 183)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jane Howard,June 2, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,June 19, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,June 12, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertie Palmer,June 18, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,June 27, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 188)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 13, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 189)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Grandpa (W. H. Davis),July 18, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),July 29, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 191)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,July 30, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 192)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),August 6, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 193)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),August 16, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 194)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,August 9, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 195)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,August 13, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 196)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,August 29, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 197)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 2, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 198)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 22, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 199)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Hattie,August 17, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 200)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),September 4, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 201)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),September 10, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 202)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),September 25, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 203)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 5, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 204)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 9, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 205)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 15, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 22, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 207)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,September 17, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 21, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 209)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mildred Jeffers,September 22, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,October 2, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),October 4, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 212)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 5, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 213)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,October 20, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 214)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),November 12, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 215)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),November 20, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 216)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),November 26, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 217)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,November 8, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 218)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,November 19, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 219)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,November 30, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 220)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 11, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 221)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Theron and Mother (NDF),December 11, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 222)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Theron and Mother (NDF),December 3, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 223)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 2, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 224)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 11, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 225)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Meda Burgess,December 7, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,January 27, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 227)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,January 21, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 228)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,January 1, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 229)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,January 7, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 230)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,January 2, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 231)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis?,January 4, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 232)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: D. E. Cramton,January 14, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 233)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,February 11, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 234)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,February 17, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 235)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,February 16, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 236)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 22, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,March 6, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 4, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 239)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Fort Wayne-Detroit, Letter of Transfer,February 6, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 240)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 1, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 25, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,March 18, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,April 1, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,April 15, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,April 26, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 5, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 17, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,April 21, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,May 1, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 250)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 4, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 251)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,May 24, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 252)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jennie Slack Cook,June 21, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 253)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 20, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 254)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,June 5, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 255)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,June 8, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 256)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,June 26, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 257)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 2, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 258)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 6, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 259)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 16, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 260)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,July 25, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 261)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Earl Fox,July 4, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 262)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,July 10, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 263)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Theron and Mother (NDF),July 30, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 264)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 19, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 8, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,August 30, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,August 13, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,August 2, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 269)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Gerty Davis,August 30, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 270)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis,August 30, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,September 4, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,September 9, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,September 15, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,September 22, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,September 25, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 276)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,September 29, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 13, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 278)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,September 23, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 279)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,September 12, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis,September 3, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 281)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis,September 29, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 282)
  - Correspondence to: Harry, W. H., and Zoe Davis From: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis,September 2, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 283)
  - Correspondence to: Harry, W. H., and Zoe Davis From: Gerty, Wilson,September 18, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 284)
  - Correspondence to: Harry, W. H., and Zoe Davis From: Wilson Davis,September 24, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 285)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,September 5, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 286)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,September 10, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 287)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,September 24, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 288)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,September 11, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 289)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,October 16, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 290)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,October 28, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 291)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mutual Hail Insurance Company,October 19, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 292)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,October 9, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 293)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,October 18, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 294)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,October 24, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,October 31, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 296)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,October 1, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis,October 5, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Ruth, Celia,October 8, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 299)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,October 2, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 300)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,October 8, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 301)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Wilson and Gerty,October 10, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 302)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis,October 13, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 303)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),October 22, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 304)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe and Zoe Davis,November 21, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 305)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe ,November 12, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 306)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry Davis,November 13, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 307)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry Davis,November 17, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 308)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Harry, and Zoe Davis,November 7, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 309)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Harry, and Zoe Davis,November 21, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 310)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 1, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 311)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 5, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 312)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,November 6, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 313)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,November 12, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 314)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,November 13, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 315)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,November 20, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 316)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),November 18, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 317)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),November 25, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 318)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),November 4, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 319)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Grandpa and Mother (NDF),November 10, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 320)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 11, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 321)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Gerty, Wilson, and Marydena Davis,November 13, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 322)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Phillipp Cerminka,November 18, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 323)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 19, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 324)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,November 25, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 325)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Earl Fox,November 21, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 326)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice,November 22, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 327)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mildred Jeffers,November 23, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 328)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,November 25, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 329)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry C. Finley,November 29, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 330)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Harry C. Finley,November 30, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 331)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),December 8, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 332)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),December 15, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 333)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),December 31, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 334)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mother (NDF),December 23, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 335)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Zoe Davis,December 3, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 336)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Zoe Davis,December 12, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 337)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Zoe Davis,December 26, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 338)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,December 14, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 339)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,December 20, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 340)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,December 4, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 341)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,December 11, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 342)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Grandpa and Mother (NDF),December 2, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 343)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),December 9, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 344)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mother (NDF),December 23, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 345)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,December 11, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 346)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Celia,December 21, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 347)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 8, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 348)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Miller,December 10, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 349)